Guide to the Sloan Program in Health Services Administration records, 1983-2012.
Sloan Program in Health Services Administration records, 1983-2010.
- Series X. Courses
  - Student Projects
    - Problem Solving Projects, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Strategic Planning Projects, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Cayuga Medical Center Cardiac Catheterization Laboratory-Project Report, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Capstone Projects-Workflow, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Capstone Projects, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Capstone Projects, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Capstone Project, April 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (1), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (2), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (3), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (4), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (5), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (6), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (7), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Capstone Project-Josh Strugatz (8), 2004 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series XI. Conferences
  - Conference-"Consumers, Information & the Evolving Healthcare Market Place" (1), April 8-9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Conference-"Consumers, Information & the Evolving Healthcare Market Place" (2), April 8-9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Management-Administrative-Curriculum-Content Clarification-by Roger Battistella-Draft, December 1991 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Conference of the American Society of Health Economists - "Health, Healthcare and Behavior" that was held in Ithaca, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Series XII. Photographs
  - Photographs, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Graduate School of Management, Fall 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Health Executives Development Program, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Health Executive Development Program, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1966-67, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sloan Program-Graduates, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sloan Program Graduation, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Certificates & Group Photo, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1998 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation-Class of 2001 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Class of 2002 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Classes of 2002 or 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Sloan Program-Graduation-Class of 2003 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Classes?, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Health Executives Development Program-Candid Photos, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Candids, 1978, 1985, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Alumni Retreat, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Candids, 1986, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Wagner Lecture-Steve Allen-Speaker, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Candids, 1995-1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Candids-NYC, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Candids, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Candids, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Candids, February 2000 (Box 5, Folder 57-60)
  - ACHE, May 2001 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Commencement-Candids, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Wagner Dinner, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - DC Intercession Trip, January 2002 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Faculty/Officers, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - M.H.A. Students, 1990's (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - MHA Graduates, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - MHA Graduates, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Students, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 69-71)
  - Photos, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 72-74)
- Series XIII. Miscellaneous
  - Faculty Biographies, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Job Descriptions- Health Services, 1999-2000, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management Organizational Chart, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Alumni Surveys, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Presidents of Sloan Alumni Association, 1961-2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)